Estefanía Márquez

Full Stack Web Developer

vsuykyasmbp@hotmail.com

Cel. +54 223 691 4591

Mar del Plata, Buenos Aires - Argentina.

LinkedIn GitHub

I'm a Full Stack web developer with experience working with React, Redux, NodeJS, SQL, MongoDB and TypeScript among other technologies. I stand out for my creative thinking, teamwork skills, self-taught capacity, great adaptability and positive thinking

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer - Crunch DNA, Inc.

Jul. 2023 - present

66 W Flagler Street STE 900 Miami, FL 33130 United States.

Development, maintenance and documentation of the first automated marketplace health diagnosis web application. Implementing interactive components and UI in close collaboration with the design and backend team. Performing automated testing and debugging of code and participating in code reviews with constructive feedback to my colleagues.

Technologies → <u>Front</u>: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Bootstrap y SASS.
App

Full Stack Web Developer - Agenddo

Nov. 2022- May 2023

Moldes 2394 1 B, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Development of a website that makes a platform available to professionals who sign up for them to control and organize their activity, and an online store for their clients to schedule their services. The app_includes: Registration and login as owner or receptionist, load of professionals, scheduling services by calendar with availability control, schedule management, customer record, online payments, notifications by emails and WhatsApp, sales and professional performance metrics.

 Technologies → <u>Front</u>: React, Redux, CSS, MUI, SDK de Mercadopago and React google charts. <u>Back</u>: Node.js with Express, implementing Cloudinary, Bcrypt, JSON Web Token, Nodemailer, Mercadopago, Mobbex and Ultramsg API. <u>Database</u>: MongoDB and Mongoose. <u>Deploy</u>: AWS, Nginx and Hostinger.

App

Full Stack Henry Assistant

Oct. 2022- Jan. 2023

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Analyze profiles and select candidates for Teaching Assistant (TA).
- Coordinate TA groups and assist them in their work, promoting further exchange and integration.
- Catalyze the ideas for improvement and concerns communicated by the TAs in action plans.
- Follow-up and analysis of the experiences of the Teaching Assistants.

Full Stack Teaching Assistant

Ago. - Oct. 2022

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Coordinate a group of students to achieve integration into their study team.

- Attend to the resolution of exercises and promote group collaboration (Pair Programming).
- Propose ideas to improve Bootcamp processes.

PROJECTS

Full Stack Web Developer - SnorInn App

Sep. - Oct. 2022

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Working with a team implementing agile development methodologies, with one-week sprints, presenting progress on the development of a complete hosting management app to a Product Owner. Where my main contributions were the creation of the user profile, controlled review form, calendar reservation system, registration/login with authentication and notifications via mail.

 Technologies → <u>Front</u>: React, Redux Toolkit, TypeScript, CSS and Bootstrap. <u>Back</u>: Node.js with Express, implementing Cloudinary, Bcrypt, JSON Web Token, Nodemailer and Stripe. <u>Database</u>: MongoDB and Mongoose.

Repository - App

Full Stack Web Developer - Pokémon App

Ago. - Sep. 2022

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Design and development of a Pokemons App with the following <u>functionalities</u>: visualization of Pokemons, route to their details, searches by name, filtering, sorting, paging and creation of pokemons.

 Technologies → Front: React, Redux, and vanilla CSS. <u>Back</u>: Node.js with Express. <u>Database</u>: PostgreSQL and Sequelize.

Repository - App

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

- Full Stack Web Developer. Henry Bootcamp. 700+ hours of theoretical-practical course. 2022.
- Professor of Higher Education. Universidad Tecnológica Nacional. 2018 2020.
- Lawyer. Facultad de Derecho de Mar del Plata. 2010 2015.

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, React Native, Redux, Django, Node.js, Express, Python, PostgreSQL, SQLite, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose, TypeScript, Bootstrap, MUI, SASS, SCRUM, Git, GitHub, AWS, Npm, JWT, API REST, Postman.

LANGUAGES

- English B2 Upper intermediate. First Certificate English.
- Japanese N4 Intermediate. Japanese-Language Proficiency.